

# CONTACT

- +8801924489215
- ✓ nihanarpa64@gmail.com
- House 251, Lane no 2, East Dolairpar, Dhaka 1236
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/arpa-nihan-4080771a0/

# **EDUCATION**

2018 - 2022
DAFFODIL INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY

- B. Sc in Computer Science & Engineering
- GPA: 3.31/4.00

2016 - 2018 DHAKA CITY COLLEGE

- Science
- GPA: 3.92/5.00

## SKILLS

- Programming Languages
   (HTML&CSS, Bootstrap,
   JavaScript, React)
- WordPress Development (create a website by WordPress using the theme, plugin with Elementor)
- Manual Testing (Black Box)
   (Functional Testing, Non-Functional Testing)
- Time Management
- Leadership
- Effective Communication
- Critical Thinking

## LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- Bangla (Fluent)

# **ARPA NIHAN**

**SOA ENGINEER** 

## PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

A dedicated Computer Science and Engineering B.Sc. graduate from Daffodil International University, currently advancing my career as a Software Quality Assurance (SQA) Engineer at Business Automation Ltd. I bring a diverse background with 2 years of experience as an English Teacher at Lightship and as the Co-Founder of 100 Million Mindset Organization, where I specialized in Graphic Design for 3 years, and Web Design and WordPress Development for 2 years. My proven ability to collaborate effectively with a wide range of international and local clients is complemented by strong communication and project management skills.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Business Automation LTD

NOVEMBER 2023 - PRESENT

Assistant SQA Engineer

• Working on three projects as an Assistant SQA Engineer.

#### Cloud Production LTD

March 2023 - October 2023

Software Developer-fresher

 Working on Website as a Software Developer-fresher. In Frontend Development I am using HTML,CSS,JS,React.

## RECENT PROJECTS

#### Online Registration System of Tour Operator and Tour Guide

- Conducted comprehensive testing, including unit, integration, system, acceptance, regression, performance, security, usability, and compatibility testing.
- Bangladesh Telecommunication Regulatory Commission (BTRC/LIMS)
  - Conducted comprehensive testing, including unit, integration, system, acceptance, regression, performance, security, usability, and compatibility testing.

## EMRD DASHBOARD

 Conducted comprehensive testing, including unit, integration, system, acceptance, regression, performance, security, usability, and compatibility testing.

## REFERENCE

### Md. Zabirul Islam

Lecturer

Phone: +8801521307471

Email: zabirul.cse@diu.edu.bd

Daffodil International University

# Md. Mojadded Hossain Khan

Assistant Project Manager

Phone: +8801632053996
Email: mojadded@ba-systems.com

**Business Automation LTD**